[
  {
    "question": "(q + 2)^2",
    "answer": "q^2 + 4q + 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c - 6)^2",
    "answer": "c^2 - 12c + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(z + 4)^2",
    "answer": "z^2 + 8z + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 3)^2",
    "answer": "a^2 + 6a + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p - 3)^2",
    "answer": "p^2 - 6p + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p + 3)^2",
    "answer": "p^2 + 6p + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(q - 1)^2",
    "answer": "q^2 - 2q + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c + 5)^2",
    "answer": "c^2 + 10c + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(y + 1)^2",
    "answer": "y^2 + 2y + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a - 5)^2",
    "answer": "a^2 - 10a + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p - 6)^2",
    "answer": "p^2 - 12p + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a - 3)^2",
    "answer": "a^2 - 6a + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x + 4)^2",
    "answer": "x^2 + 8x + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(z + 1)^2",
    "answer": "z^2 + 2z + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + 5)^2",
    "answer": "b^2 + 10b + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + 6)^2",
    "answer": "b^2 + 12b + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x + 4)^2",
    "answer": "x^2 + 8x + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x - 4)^2",
    "answer": "x^2 - 8x + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(z - 4)^2",
    "answer": "z^2 - 8z + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(q - 2)^2",
    "answer": "q^2 - 4q + 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(q + 3)^2",
    "answer": "q^2 + 6q + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x - 1)^2",
    "answer": "x^2 - 2x + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m + 1)^2",
    "answer": "m^2 + 2m + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x - 5)^2",
    "answer": "x^2 - 10x + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x - 6)^2",
    "answer": "x^2 - 12x + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + 6)^2",
    "answer": "b^2 + 12b + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(z - 3)^2",
    "answer": "z^2 - 6z + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a - 4)^2",
    "answer": "a^2 - 8a + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p - 4)^2",
    "answer": "p^2 - 8p + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(y - 1)^2",
    "answer": "y^2 - 2y + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x - 5)^2",
    "answer": "x^2 - 10x + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m - 1)^2",
    "answer": "m^2 - 2m + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(q - 1)^2",
    "answer": "q^2 - 2q + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x - 5)^2",
    "answer": "x^2 - 10x + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x + 4)^2",
    "answer": "x^2 + 8x + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p + 4)^2",
    "answer": "p^2 + 8p + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x - 4)^2",
    "answer": "x^2 - 8x + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + 6)^2",
    "answer": "b^2 + 12b + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p + 6)^2",
    "answer": "p^2 + 12p + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p - 4)^2",
    "answer": "p^2 - 8p + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b - 1)^2",
    "answer": "b^2 - 2b + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c + 5)^2",
    "answer": "c^2 + 10c + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(q + 1)^2",
    "answer": "q^2 + 2q + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x - 1)^2",
    "answer": "x^2 - 2x + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c - 3)^2",
    "answer": "c^2 - 6c + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m - 6)^2",
    "answer": "m^2 - 12m + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m + 2)^2",
    "answer": "m^2 + 4m + 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 5)^2",
    "answer": "a^2 + 10a + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(z - 4)^2",
    "answer": "z^2 - 8z + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b - 3)^2",
    "answer": "b^2 - 6b + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n + m)^2",
    "answer": "m^2 + 2mn + n^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p + 4n)^2",
    "answer": "16n^2 + 8np + p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(z - 6p)^2",
    "answer": "36p^2 - 12pz + z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x + 3m)^2",
    "answer": "9m^2 + 6mx + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n + 3m)^2",
    "answer": "9m^2 + 6mn + n^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b - 2z)^2",
    "answer": "b^2 - 4bz + 4z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + p)^2",
    "answer": "a^2 + 2ap + p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(q - 4m)^2",
    "answer": "16m^2 - 8mq + q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(z - p)^2",
    "answer": "p^2 - 2pz + z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(y - 4p)^2",
    "answer": "16p^2 - 8py + y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(y - 2p)^2",
    "answer": "4p^2 - 4py + y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c + 4n)^2",
    "answer": "c^2 + 8cn + 16n^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(z + m)^2",
    "answer": "m^2 + 2mz + z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p + b)^2",
    "answer": "b^2 + 2bp + p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + 2x)^2",
    "answer": "b^2 + 4bx + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + q)^2",
    "answer": "b^2 + 2bq + q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n + 4c)^2",
    "answer": "16c^2 + 8cn + n^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 2x)^2",
    "answer": "a^2 + 4ax + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c + 4x)^2",
    "answer": "c^2 + 8cx + 16x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m + 3b)^2",
    "answer": "9b^2 + 6bm + m^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n + 5x)^2",
    "answer": "n^2 + 10nx + 25x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(y - 2x)^2",
    "answer": "4x^2 - 4xy + y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + n)^2",
    "answer": "a^2 + 2an + n^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 3c)^2",
    "answer": "a^2 + 6ac + 9c^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b - 4c)^2",
    "answer": "b^2 - 8bc + 16c^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p + 3q)^2",
    "answer": "p^2 + 6pq + 9q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x - z)^2",
    "answer": "x^2 - 2xz + z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m + 2y)^2",
    "answer": "m^2 + 4my + 4y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m - a)^2",
    "answer": "a^2 - 2am + m^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x + p)^2",
    "answer": "p^2 + 2px + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n - 6x)^2",
    "answer": "n^2 - 12nx + 36x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m - 5b)^2",
    "answer": "25b^2 - 10bm + m^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(y - 4p)^2",
    "answer": "16p^2 - 8py + y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(y + n)^2",
    "answer": "n^2 + 2ny + y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m + 2q)^2",
    "answer": "m^2 + 4mq + 4q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(z - 3q)^2",
    "answer": "9q^2 - 6qz + z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m - 2z)^2",
    "answer": "m^2 - 4mz + 4z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c + 3x)^2",
    "answer": "c^2 + 6cx + 9x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n - p)^2",
    "answer": "n^2 - 2np + p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n - 6c)^2",
    "answer": "36c^2 - 12cn + n^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 3c)^2",
    "answer": "a^2 + 6ac + 9c^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(y + 6z)^2",
    "answer": "y^2 + 12yz + 36z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(z - 6m)^2",
    "answer": "36m^2 - 12mz + z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x - p)^2",
    "answer": "p^2 - 2px + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(y - 2m)^2",
    "answer": "4m^2 - 4my + y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n - 6q)^2",
    "answer": "n^2 - 12nq + 36q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(y + 3b)^2",
    "answer": "9b^2 + 6by + y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n + 5y)^2",
    "answer": "n^2 + 10ny + 25y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p - 2b)^2",
    "answer": "4b^2 - 4bp + p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n + 2x)^2",
    "answer": "n^2 + 4nx + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2q - 3)^2",
    "answer": "4q^2 - 12q + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3x - 4)^2",
    "answer": "9x^2 - 24x + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3z - 4)^2",
    "answer": "9z^2 - 24z + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + 3)^2",
    "answer": "b^2 + 6b + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2p - 2)^2",
    "answer": "4p^2 - 8p + 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 4)^2",
    "answer": "a^2 + 8a + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2z - 2)^2",
    "answer": "4z^2 - 8z + 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m - 3)^2",
    "answer": "m^2 - 6m + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m - 6)^2",
    "answer": "m^2 - 12m + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3q + 4)^2",
    "answer": "9q^2 + 24q + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(q + 1)^2",
    "answer": "q^2 + 2q + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p + 5)^2",
    "answer": "p^2 + 10p + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3c - 4)^2",
    "answer": "9c^2 - 24c + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2n + 6)^2",
    "answer": "4n^2 + 24n + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p + 3)^2",
    "answer": "p^2 + 6p + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + 4)^2",
    "answer": "b^2 + 8b + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2p - 1)^2",
    "answer": "4p^2 - 4p + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3y + 6)^2",
    "answer": "9y^2 + 36y + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2p - 1)^2",
    "answer": "4p^2 - 4p + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3b + 5)^2",
    "answer": "9b^2 + 30b + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(y + 4)^2",
    "answer": "y^2 + 8y + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(y - 5)^2",
    "answer": "y^2 - 10y + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x - 1)^2",
    "answer": "x^2 - 2x + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x + 1)^2",
    "answer": "x^2 + 2x + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3x - 3)^2",
    "answer": "9x^2 - 18x + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2c - 1)^2",
    "answer": "4c^2 - 4c + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2m - 5)^2",
    "answer": "4m^2 - 20m + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3q - 3)^2",
    "answer": "9q^2 - 18q + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2q + 4)^2",
    "answer": "4q^2 + 16q + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(q - 3)^2",
    "answer": "q^2 - 6q + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x + 6)^2",
    "answer": "x^2 + 12x + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2q + 1)^2",
    "answer": "4q^2 + 4q + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2p + 6)^2",
    "answer": "4p^2 + 24p + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3a + 4)^2",
    "answer": "9a^2 + 24a + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2c + 5)^2",
    "answer": "4c^2 + 20c + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c + 3)^2",
    "answer": "c^2 + 6c + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2x + 1)^2",
    "answer": "4x^2 + 4x + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(z - 2)^2",
    "answer": "z^2 - 4z + 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(z + 6)^2",
    "answer": "z^2 + 12z + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2a - 4)^2",
    "answer": "4a^2 - 16a + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c + 4)^2",
    "answer": "c^2 + 8c + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2x + 5)^2",
    "answer": "4x^2 + 20x + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2b - 1)^2",
    "answer": "4b^2 - 4b + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2x - 3)^2",
    "answer": "4x^2 - 12x + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3c + 6)^2",
    "answer": "9c^2 + 36c + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3x - 3)^2",
    "answer": "9x^2 - 18x + 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b - 6)^2",
    "answer": "b^2 - 12b + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a - 4)^2",
    "answer": "a^2 - 8a + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3m - 6)^2",
    "answer": "9m^2 - 36m + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3p + 5)^2",
    "answer": "9p^2 + 30p + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2c + 3b)^2",
    "answer": "9b^2 + 12bc + 4c^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2q - 3b)^2",
    "answer": "9b^2 - 12bq + 4q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2q - 5x)^2",
    "answer": "4q^2 - 20qx + 25x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3n - 2a)^2",
    "answer": "4a^2 - 12an + 9n^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3n - 3b)^2",
    "answer": "9b^2 - 18bn + 9n^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2y + 4m)^2",
    "answer": "16m^2 + 16my + 4y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3q + 3m)^2",
    "answer": "9m^2 + 18mq + 9q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3p + 2y)^2",
    "answer": "9p^2 + 12py + 4y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3b + 4c)^2",
    "answer": "9b^2 + 24bc + 16c^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2n + c)^2",
    "answer": "c^2 + 4cn + 4n^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2c + 5n)^2",
    "answer": "4c^2 + 20cn + 25n^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3x + b)^2",
    "answer": "b^2 + 6bx + 9x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3a + 3m)^2",
    "answer": "9a^2 + 18am + 9m^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2x + 3n)^2",
    "answer": "9n^2 + 12nx + 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2a + 5y)^2",
    "answer": "4a^2 + 20ay + 25y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n - 6a)^2",
    "answer": "36a^2 - 12an + n^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 3c)^2",
    "answer": "a^2 + 6ac + 9c^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2q - 4b)^2",
    "answer": "16b^2 - 16bq + 4q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2q - 5m)^2",
    "answer": "25m^2 - 20mq + 4q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2p - 6y)^2",
    "answer": "4p^2 - 24py + 36y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c - 5x)^2",
    "answer": "c^2 - 10cx + 25x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2p + 6c)^2",
    "answer": "36c^2 + 24cp + 4p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3n - 4m)^2",
    "answer": "16m^2 - 24mn + 9n^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2c - m)^2",
    "answer": "4c^2 - 4cm + m^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3p + 2m)^2",
    "answer": "4m^2 + 12mp + 9p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2z + 2q)^2",
    "answer": "4q^2 + 8qz + 4z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 5m)^2",
    "answer": "a^2 + 10am + 25m^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2a + x)^2",
    "answer": "4a^2 + 4ax + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2n - 3y)^2",
    "answer": "4n^2 - 12ny + 9y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2a + 4x)^2",
    "answer": "4a^2 + 16ax + 16x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2c + 5p)^2",
    "answer": "4c^2 + 20cp + 25p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2a - b)^2",
    "answer": "4a^2 - 4ab + b^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3a - x)^2",
    "answer": "9a^2 - 6ax + x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(q - 6x)^2",
    "answer": "q^2 - 12qx + 36x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3p + 4m)^2",
    "answer": "16m^2 + 24mp + 9p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3m + 4z)^2",
    "answer": "9m^2 + 24mz + 16z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3y - 3x)^2",
    "answer": "9x^2 - 18xy + 9y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3m + 6a)^2",
    "answer": "36a^2 + 36am + 9m^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2q + 3n)^2",
    "answer": "9n^2 + 12nq + 4q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3y + 6c)^2",
    "answer": "36c^2 + 36cy + 9y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3b + 5a)^2",
    "answer": "25a^2 + 30ab + 9b^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3a - 6z)^2",
    "answer": "9a^2 - 36az + 36z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2m + 6a)^2",
    "answer": "36a^2 + 24am + 4m^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2z - 5a)^2",
    "answer": "25a^2 - 20az + 4z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3b - 5y)^2",
    "answer": "9b^2 - 30by + 25y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2c + 6z)^2",
    "answer": "4c^2 + 24cz + 36z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3a + z)^2",
    "answer": "9a^2 + 6az + z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2a + m)^2",
    "answer": "4a^2 + 4am + m^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3z - 5a)^2",
    "answer": "25a^2 - 30az + 9z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2y + 4z)^2",
    "answer": "4y^2 + 16yz + 16z^2"
  }
]